Gross, James A. Arbitration Files 5697
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Borden Chemical, Division of Borden, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Bainbridge Lodge No. 1278, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Borden Chemical, Division of Borden, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Bainbridge Lodge No. 1278, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Borden Chemical, Division of Borden, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Bainbridge Lodge No. 1278, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Bossert Manufacturing Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District Lodge No. 157, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  Stipulated Award. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Employee Preference. EX, AN, RC, A.
- Bossert Manufacturing Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District Lodge No. 157, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Buffalo Board of Education vs. Professional, Clerical and Technical Employees Association, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  Issue: Arbitrability--Grievance Procedure, Failure To Follow; Classification of Jobs--Duties Performed. EX, AN, RC, A.
- Buffalo Board of Education vs. Professional, Clerical and Technical Employees Association, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Buffalo Board of Education vs. Buffalo Council of Supervisors and Administrators, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Issue: Classification of Jobs--Discontinuance of Classification and Job. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Buffalo Board of Education vs. Buffalo Council of Supervisors and Administrators, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Buffalo Board of Education vs. Buffalo Council of Supervisors and Administrators, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Buffalo Board of Education vs. Buffalo Council of Supervisors and Administrators, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Buffalo Board of Education vs. Buffalo Council of Supervisors and Administrators (Box 9, Folder 5)
  NA, AN, RC. Cancelled(?).
- Buffalo Board of Education vs. Buffalo Teachers Federation, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Qualifications. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Buffalo Board of Education vs. Buffalo Teachers Federation, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Buffalo Board of Education vs. Buffalo Teachers Federation, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Buffalo Board of Education vs. Buffalo Teachers Federation, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Buffalo Board of Education vs. Buffalo Teachers Federation, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  Issue: Union Representatives and Business--Representatives' Authority. EX, AN, RC, A.
- Buffalo Board of Education vs. Buffalo Teachers Federation, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Buffalo, City of vs. Buffalo Police Benevolent Association, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Seniority. EX, AN, RC.
- Buffalo, City of vs. Buffalo Police Benevolent Association, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Buffalo, City of vs. Buffalo Police Benevolent Association, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Buffalo General Hospital vs. Communications Workers of America, Local 1168, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  NA, RC.
- Buffalo General Hospital vs. Communications Workers of America, Local 1168, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Shift Referencing. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Buffalo General Hospital vs. Communications Workers of America, Local 1168, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Buffalo General Hospital vs. Communications Workers of America, Local 1168, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Cargill, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge No. 1607, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  Issue: Posting--Refusal To Post. EX, AN. RC, A, SD.
- Cargill, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge No. 1607, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Cargill, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Cayuga Lodge No. 1607, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  Issue: Overtime--Out-of- Classification Assignment. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Cargill, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Cayuga Lodge No. 1607, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Carhart Photo, Incorporated of Syracuse, NY vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 317, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  Issue: Seniority--Recall. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Carhart Photo, Incorporated of Syracuse, NY vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 317, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Carrier Corporation vs. Sheet Metal Workers International Association, Local Union 527, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  Issue: Termination of Employment--Failure To Report After Recall. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Carrier Corporation vs. Sheet Metal Workers International Association, Local Union 527, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Carrier Corporation vs. Sheet Metal Workers International Association, Local Union 527, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Carrier Corporation vs. Sheet Metal Workers International Association, Local Union 527, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Carrier Corporation vs. Independent Union of Plant Protection Employees, Local No. 7, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  Issue: Discipline--Discharge; Improper Job Attitude-- Sleeping On The Job. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Carrier Corporation vs. Independent Union of Plant Protection Employees, Local No. 7, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Carrier Corporation vs. Independent Union of Plant Protection Employees, Local No. 7, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Carrier Corporation vs. Sheet Metal Workers International Association, Local Union No. 527, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  Issue: Discipline--Discharge. EX, AN, RC, A.
- Carrier Corporation vs. Sheet Metal Workers International Association, Local Union No. 527, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Carrols Distribution Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 317, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  Issue: Discipline--Discharge; Fights and Altercations-- Assault on Supervisor. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Carrols Distribution Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 317, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Carrols Distribution Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 317, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Chemung, County of vs. Helen Ryder, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  Issue: Discipline--Knowledge of Violation. EX, AN, RC, SD.
- Chemung, County of vs. Helen Ryder, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Chemung, County of vs. Helen Ryder, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Chemung, County of vs. Helen Ryder, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Chemung, County of vs. Helen Ryder, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- CNY Centro, Incorporated vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 580, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Issue: Contract Interpretation--Rates of Pay. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- CNY Centro, Incorporated vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 580, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- CNY Centro, Incorporated vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 580, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- East Irondequoit Central School District vs. East Irondequoit Teachers' Association, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  Issue: Termination of Employment--Severance Pay. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- East Irondequoit Central School District vs. East Irondequoit Teachers' Association, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- East Irondequoit Central School District vs. East Irondequoit Teachers' Association, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Ellis Hospital vs. New York State Nurses Association, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  Issue: Reduction in Force--Layoff. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Ellis Hospital vs. New York State Nurses Association, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Ellis Hospital vs. New York State Nurses Association, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Ellis Hospital vs. New York State Nurses Association, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Elmira City School District vs. Elmira Teachers' Association, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  Issue: Arbitrability--Assignment of Jobs. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Elmira City School District vs. Elmira Teachers' Association, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Elmira City School District vs. Elmira Teachers' Association (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Elmira City School District vs. Instructional Support Education Association (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Erie, County of vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Council 82 and Local 2060, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  Issue: Apprentices, Learners, and Trainees--Rates of Pay. EX, AN, RC, A.
- Ernst Steel Corporation (Ernst Construction Division) vs. Shopmen's Local 576, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  Issue: Recall--Discrimination. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Ernst Steel Corporation (Ernst Construction Division) vs. Shopmen's Local 576, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Ernst Steel Corporation (Ernst Construction Division) vs. Shopmen's Local 576, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Ernst Steel Corporation (Ernst Construction Division) vs. Shopmen's Local 576, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Fort Plain Central School District vs. Michael Subik, Respondent Tenured Teacher, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  Issue: Improper Personal Conduct--Dishonesty. AN, RC, SD.
- Fort Plain Central School District vs. Michael Subik, Respondent Tenured Teacher, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Fort Plain Central School District vs. Michael Subik, Respondent Tenured Teacher, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Fort Plain Central School District vs. Michael Subik, Respondent Tenured Teacher, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Fruehauf Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, Local 317, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  Issue: Discipline--Layoff As Discipline. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Fruehauf Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, Local 317, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Fruehauf Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, Local 317, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- GAF Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local No. 1807, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  Issue: Contract Interpretation--Lunch Periods. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- GAF Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local No. 1807, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- GAF Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local No. 1807, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- GAF Corporation vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 306, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  Issue: Classification of Jobs--New Classification. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- GAF Corporation vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 306, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- GAF Corporation vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 306, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- GAF Corporation vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 306, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Goulds Pumps, Incorporated, Engineered Products Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local No. 3298, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  Issue: Discipline-- Discharge; Falsification--Daily Time Record. EX, AN. RC, A, SD.
- Goulds Pumps, Incorporated, Engineered Products Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local No. 3298, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Goulds Pumps, Incorporated, Engineered Products Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local No. 3298, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Goulds Pumps, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local No. 3298, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  Issue: Contract Interpretation--Layoff Procedures. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Goulds Pumps, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local No. 3298, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Goulds Pumps, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local No. 3298, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Grace, W.R. and Company, Evans Chemetics Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, Local Union No. 7110, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Grace, W.R. and Company, Evans Chemetics Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, Local Union No. 7110, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Grace, W.R. and Company, Evans Chemetics Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, Local Union No. 7110, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Groton School District vs. Groton Faculty Association, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Added Duties. TR, EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Groton School District vs. Groton Faculty Association, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Groton School District vs. Groton Faculty Association, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Groton School District vs. Groton Faculty Association, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Herman DeKalb Central School District vs. Ronald Turbide (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Issue: Insubordination--Failure To Obey Orders (Section 3020-A Education Law Proceeding). EX, AN, RC, SD.
- Herman DeKalb Central School District vs. Ronald Turbide (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Herman DeKalb Central School District vs. Ronald Turbide (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Herman DeKalb Central School District vs. Ronald Turbide (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Hilton Central School District vs. Hilton Central School Teachers' Association, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  Issue: Leaves of Absence--Vacation Eligibility (sabbatical). EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Hilton Central School District vs. Hilton Central School Teachers' Association, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Hilton Central School District vs. Hilton Central School Teachers' Association, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Holland Patent Central School District vs. Holland Patent Teachers' Association (Box 11, Folder 8)
  NA, EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Holland Patent Central School District vs. Holland Patent Teachers' Association (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Holland Patent Central School District vs. Holland Patent Teachers' Association (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Holland Patent Central School District vs. Holland Patent Teachers' Association (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Hooker Chemical Corporation, Durez Plastics Division vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 2112, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  Issue: Classification of Jobs--Assignment To Work Outside Classification. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Hooker Chemical Corporation, Durez Plastics Division vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 2112, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Hooker Chemical Corporation, Durez Plastics Division vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 2112, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Horseheads Central School District vs. Horseheads Teachers' Association, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  Issue: Schedules of Work--Change of Schedule. EX, AN, RC, A.
- Horseheads Central School District vs. Horseheads Teachers' Association, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Horseheads Central School District vs. Horseheads Teachers' Association, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- International Salt Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local Union No. 12460, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  Issue: Discipline--Discharge; Fights and Altercations--Assault on Supervisor. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- International Salt Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local Union No. 12460, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- International Salt Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local Union No. 12460, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- International Salt Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 12460, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  Issue: Contracting Out--Repair Work. EX, AN, RC, A.
- International Salt Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 12460, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- International Salt Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 12460, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Interstate Brands, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, Local No. 693, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  Issue: Rates of Pay--Commissions. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Interstate Brands, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, Local No. 693, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Interstate Brands, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, Local No. 693, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Ithaca City School District vs. Ithaca Teachers Association, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Transfer of Work. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Ithaca City School District vs. Ithaca Teachers Association, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Ithaca City School District vs. Ithaca Teachers Association, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Ithaca City School District vs. Ithaca Teachers Association, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Ithaca City School District vs. Ithaca Teachers Association, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Ithaca City School District vs. Ithaca Teachers Association, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Ithaca City School District vs. Ithaca City School District Employees Association, Faculty Association of Jamestown Community College AFL-CIO, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  Issue: Termination of Employment--Disability. EX, AN, RC, SD.
- Ithaca City School District vs. Ithaca City School District Employees Association, Faculty Association of Jamestown Community College AFL-CIO, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Ithaca City School District vs. Ithaca City School District Employees Association, Faculty Association of Jamestown Community College AFL-CIO, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Kennedy Valve Division, ITT Grinnal Valve Company, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District Lodge No. 58, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Issue: Discipline--Discharge; Improper Job Attitude--Sleeping On Job. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Kennedy Valve Division, ITT Grinnal Valve Company, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District Lodge No. 58, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Kennedy Valve Division, ITT Grinnal Valve Company, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District Lodge No. 58, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Label Processing Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  Issue: Layoff--Notice. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Label Processing Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Lakeside Nursing Home vs. General Service Employees Union (SEIU), Local 200, AFL-CIO, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  Issue: Discipline--Transfer, Denial. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Lakeside Nursing Home vs. General Service Employees Union (SEIU), Local 200, AFL-CIO, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Lakeside Nursing Home vs. General Service Employees Union (SEIU), Local 200, AFL-CIO, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Lakeside Nursing Home vs. General Service Employees Union (SEIU), Local 200, AFL-CIO, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Lewis County vs. Civil Service Employees Association (Box 12, Folder 10)
  NA, TR, EX, AN, RC.
- Lewis County vs. Civil Service Employees Association (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Lewis County vs. Civil Service Employees Association (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Lipe Rollway Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local No. 14929, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  Issue: Vacation Pay--Eligibility. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Lipe Rollway Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local No. 14929, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Monarch Machine Tool Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local No. 802, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Assignment To Work Outside Classification. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Monarch Machine Tool Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local No. 802, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Monarch Machine Tool Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local No. 802, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Monarch Machine Tool Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local No. 802, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Monroe County (Monroe County Hospital) vs. Civil Service Employees Association, Local No. 828 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  Issue: Termination of Employment--Discharge vs. Quits. NA, EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Monroe County (Monroe County Hospital) vs. Civil Service Employees Association, Local No. 828 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Monroe County (Monroe County Hospital) vs. Civil Service Employees Association, Local No. 828 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Muench-Kreuzer Candle Company, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local Union No. 15310, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Muench-Kreuzer Candle Company, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local Union No. 15310, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- National Fuel and Gas Distribution Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 2154, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  Issue: Promotions--Ability vs. Seniority. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- National Fuel and Gas Distribution Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 2154, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- National Fuel and Gas Distribution Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 2154, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- National Fuel and Gas Distribution Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 2154, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- National Fuel and Gas Distribution Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 2154, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- National Fuel and Gas Distribution Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local No. 2154, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  Issue: Classification of Jobs--Disabled Employee. NA, EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- National Fuel and Gas Distribution Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local No. 2154, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- National Fuel and Gas Distribution Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local No. 2154, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- National Fuel and Gas Distribution Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local No. 2154, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- National Fuel and Gas Distribution Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local No. 2154, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- National Fuel and Gas Distribution Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local No. 2154, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- National Fuel and Gas Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local No. 2154, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  Issue: Contract Interpretation--Job Descriptions. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- National Fuel and Gas Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local No. 2154, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- New Berlin Central School vs. New Berlin Faculty Association, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  Issue: Arbitrability--Job Classification. EX, AN, RC, A.
- New Berlin Central School vs. New Berlin Faculty Association, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- New Berlin Central School vs. New Berlin Faculty Association, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- New Berlin Central School vs. New Berlin Faculty Association, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- New Berlin Central School vs. New Berlin Faculty Association, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- New York Air Brake Company vs. The International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge No. 761, District 137, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  Issue: Schedules of Work--Inventory Shutdown. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- New York Air Brake Company vs. The International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge No. 761, District 137, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- New York Air Brake Company vs. The International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge No. 761, District 137, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- New York Air Brake Company vs. The International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge No. 761, District 137, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- New York State Electric and Gas Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, System Council U-7, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  Issue: Schedules of Work--Time Off Schedules. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.